Ruslan Popov

Moscow, Russia +79772695370 me@ruslanpopov.com

I'm Full-stack Software Developer who always keen to learn new things. Have enough experience using both Ruby on Rails and React/Mobx (include SSR) development and related technologies. Have wide knowledge of modern web development. Understand Docker, Kubernetes, AWS. Know how databases work, either relational or non-relational.

Work Experience

Full-stack Software Developer

05/2019 to Present

Overteam

Moscow, Russia

I developed medonline.sogaz.ru - service which helping Sogaz customers get an appointment with a doctor. This service works with about 160 clinics throughout Russia. I also develop and maintain sanatory.ru - the largest Russian sanatorium booking service.

Full-stack Software Developer

08/2015 to 05/2019

Interfax

Moscow, Russia

I developed and maintained of xco-interfax.ru and xco.news. Worked with a wide range of tasks e.g.: divided a monolithic application into microservices, migrated the frontend of xco-interfax.ru to SPA, migrated of deploying from Capistrano to Teamcity CI, implemented API integrations with spark-interfax.ru and scan-interfax.ru.

Full-stack Software Developer

04/2013 to 08/2015

Milk

Moscow, Russia

I helped to automate business processes at Milk, the Russian independent creative agency. I developed in-house ERP & HRM services, which helping manage and grow the company.

Full-stack Software Developer

04/2012 to 04/2013

Kodix

Moscow, Russia

I developed and maintained different kinds of web projects like online shops, magazines, vehicle dealers websites and more.

PHP developer

03/2009 to 03/2012

Eto Legko

Moscow, Russia

I developed and maintained various web sites which used Bitrix CMS.

Skills

Ruby on Rails - 8 years

React - 4 years

Mobx - 1 year

Docker - 3 years

Kubernetes - 1 year

Git - 7 years

Javascript - 10+ years

Education

State University for Humanities and Technology

Bachelor's

History

Orekhovo-Zuevo, Russia

09/2009 to 06/2015

Links

https://ruslanpopov.com

https://github.com/heckfy

https://www.linkedin.com/in/i-ruslan-popov